

SUMMARY

Experienced Backend Engineer with excellent client and project management skills. Actionoriented with strong ability to communicate effectively with technology, executive and business audiences. Highlymotivated Backend experienced in delivering quality results across demanding projects. Applies excellent systems understanding and engineering knowledge to resolve complex technical issues. Evolves thinking and practices to improve department abilities and opportunities.

SKILLS

- JavaScript
- Communication skills
- Knowledge of Laravel
- Problem-solving
- HTML
- Apache web server
- API Development
- Fast Learner

LANGUAGES

Indonesian: First Language

English:

В1

Intermediate

MOHAMMAD RIFQI

Bekasi, Indonesia, Jawa Barat, 17124

082111768038

⋪ hallo@akmalrifqi.my.id

EXPERIENCE

May 2021 - Current

Freelance Fullstack Engineer PT. Informasi Teknologi Indonesia | Jakarta, Jawa Barat, Indonesia

 Unilever Indonesia - Currently creating and maintaining website features based on Laravel as a backend and HTML, CSS & Javascript for the frontend. Handling over thousands data record from many schemas and tables postgreSQL.

August 2022 - January 2023

Freelance Backend Engineer PT. Ditama Inti Teknologi | Jakarta, Jawa Barat, Indonesia

 Developing fintech web application using Laravel Framework. This application can topup, send, and disburst user money using Flip as the payment gateway.

November 2021 - January 2022

Backend Developer Intern PT. Kreatifhub Inti Nusantara (kreatifhub.com) | Jakarta, Jawa Barat, Indonesia

April 2021 - May 2021

Backend Developer Intern PT. Omnitech Meta Kreasi | Jakarta, Jawa Barat, Indonesia

January 2017 - May 2017

IT Support Technician PT. Andalas Media Informatika | Jakarta, Jawa Barat, Indonesia

EDUCATION

2023

Bachelor of Information System | Information System Universitas Gunadarma, Bekasi, Indonesia

2018

Vocational High School | Teknik Komputer Jaringan SMKN 1 KOTA BEKASI, Bekasi, Indonesia